dimmi.com.au 2014-05-17

# Privacy Policy - Dimmi

**SCOPE**

This statement applies to Dimmi Pty Limited.

Dimmi Pty Limited is bound by the National Privacy Principles (NPP) which are set out in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). The NPP's can be found at [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.com.au/ "Privacy")

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We may collect information directly from you, when you register as a member or make a reservation on our website or a website of one of our affiliate or restaurant partners, subscribe to our newsletters, write to us, telephone us or email us. This will usually include your name and all of your contact details, for the purpose of making a restaurant reservation.

We may use cookies and other technologies to keep track of your interactions with our sites and services to offer a personalised experience.

**USES OF INFORMATION**

We use information about you for responding to and fulfilling your requests for our products and services. This includes sending you automated service messages related to your upcoming or recent restaurant reservations, such as confirmations, reminders, and/or invitations to provide user reviews & ratings.

Please note that although information which you provide, when you register with Dimmi or make a restaurant reservation or submit a review or other content for publication or sharing will not be used in any unsolicited communication or for which you do not provide consent, you automatically consent for us to treat your personal data in accordance with our privacy policy and for the purposes described below.   You should also note that for our services to operate efficiently, you cannot unsubscribe from service messages.

We might send you newsletters or promotional offers from time to time. We will only send these if you have NOT opted out to receive them. Our newsletters provide general news, information about the latest deals, and occasionally offer incentives for completing surveys or participating in competitions or promotions.

Where you have consented to receive marketing communications from Dimmi, you may from time to time receive communications relating to special offers and/or promotions.

We use information about you to help us to identify other services that might be beneficial to you, and to inform you about them and other items of interest.

We use information about you to help us with our internal accounting and administration, and to protect you and us from fraud.

We do NOT share any personal information about you with anyone, other than as outlined in this agreement, as may be required by law, or as needed by us to assist in managing our relationship with you.

The Internet is not a secure environment. If you send us information, including your email address, it is sent at your own risk.

**OTHER INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

**Statistical information**

When you visit our site, we record general information about your visit for statistical purposes.

**Cookies**

We may, from time to time, use "cookies" to store your preferences, record session information and collect information on how you visit and access our web pages. We collect information on the web pages visited by our customers to help us continue to improve our services.

Cookies are pieces of information that our web page transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site.

We may also use devices called "web beacons" to help us identify when emails sent to you have been received and read. In order to prevent the introduction of viruses and hackers into the Dimmi site we may collect information, such as IP addresses, into a log file to be used to identify potential hackers of the Dimmi site.

Similarly when you click on a link hosted on our site and are redirected to some other site your personal information including your IP address may be collected by that other site when recording your visit to that site. These third party websites are not under the control of Dimmi and we are not responsible for the content or the conduct of any such third party site. Before disclosing any further personal information on any website accessed via Dimmi we suggest you examine the terms and conditions and privacy policy of that third party site.

The use of cookies is an industry standard and many websites use them to provide useful features for you. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify you, only your computer.

You can delete cookies from your computer at any time (see your internet browser's help menu for more information); however, this will remove all cookies and not just those associated with the dimmi.com.au site. You can individually remove a cookie that connects a property to your shortlist by clicking the remove option when the property appears in your shortlist.

**Your Choices**

You may opt out of receiving promotional material from us by removing the tick from the Opt box. IF YOU DO NOT, YOU WILL AUTOMATICALLY BE DEEMED TO HAVE OPTED IN. You may access the personal information we hold about you, and ask us to correct any errors.

**Who We Share Your Information With**

We do not disclose any information about customer bookings to anyone except in the following circumstances:

**Restaurants**

We provide key information including your name, telephone number and email address for each booking made to the relevant restaurant. Restaurants require this information for the booking and may use it if they need to contact you about the booking. We have placed limitations on these restaurants from using or disclosing your information without your permission. Despite this, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of any restaurant or other service provider whose services you utilise via our website.You should note that unless you have un-ticked the box on the booking sheet, you have expressly agreed to the relevant restaurant sending you marketing and other material. Dimmi plays no role in the content, frequency, timing or unsubscription process of any restaurant's marketing communications. If you would like to unsubscribe from a restaurant's marketing communications, please contact the appropriate restaurant directly.

**Affiliate Partners**

If you have made your booking through an affiliate partner, then similarly, you should note that unless you have un-ticked the box on the booking sheet, you have expressly agreed to that affiliate partner (and the relevant restaurant) sending you marketing and other material. We have placed limitations on these affiliate partners from using or disclosing your information without your permission. Despite this, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of the relevant affiliate partner. You may also consent to receive marketing communications from the website at which you've made a reservation. Dimmi plays no role in the content, frequency, timing or un-subscription process of any affiliate partners restaurant's marketing communications. If you would like to unsubscribe from an affiliate partners marketing communications, please contact the appropriate affiliate partner directly.

**Facebook and Twitter (and other social networks)**

You may use our services to share your restaurant experiences or preferences on a social network, blog or social media portal such as Facebook or Twitter.  Guidelines on posting of reviews and other content may be found on dimmi.com.au When you do use our system to share your views, your personal information submitted with your Posting will be automatically transmitted to that other system. When you register with Dimmi, submit a Posting or make a restaurant reservation, you are consenting to us sharing your personal information with the social network on which you have shared your Posting.

You may opt out of sharing activities in the manner described below in the section headed "How to control and access your Information"

**Third Party Service Providers**

In order to maintain our website and enhance our communications with you, our channel partners and affiliates we may have to disclose your personal information to third-party service providers for this purpose.

Other than as set out above or to comply with our legal obligations below, we will not disclose your personal information to any other party without your consent nor will we sell or exchange your personal information with any other party.

**Legal obligations**

We may be required from time to time by law or industry regulatory bodies to disclose information you have provided to us. We may also disclose information about someone who poses a threat to our interests (such as customer fraud) or whose activities could cause harm to others.

**HOW YOU CONTROL AND ACCESS YOUR INFORMATION**

You are able to control and have access to your information:

Newsletter subscription and unsubscription

If at any time you would like to either change your email address with us or unsubscribe from our newsletter or promotional correspondence, you can:

  1. Go to the "Privacy" section on our website and follow the instructions to change your email address or unsubscribe; or
  2. Send an email to [unsubscribe@dimmi.com.au](mailto:unsubscribe@dimmi.com.au?subject=Unsubscribe%20me%20from%20Dimmi "Unsubscribe from Dimmi") advising that you would like to unsubscribe or change your email address. Be sure to include details of your old and new email addresses for changes.

**General**

If at any time you wish to enquire about any of your personal information which we store, please contact us.

**HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

To ensure the confidentiality of your personal information, we use leading security technology and procedures that are regularly reviewed and updated.

**CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

We may occasionally make changes to our privacy policy or practices. You should constantly review this page for any changes. We will notify you of any changes in our privacy policy by posting the modifications on our website or otherwise informing you before we use your personal information in any way not previously disclosed in our privacy policy.

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

For more information, you may obtain a printed copy of our Privacy Policy by writing to us at Suite 5, Level 2, 12-16 Chippen St, Chippendale NSW 2008 or send us an email [privacy@dimmi.com.au](mailto:privacy@dimmi.com.au).
